let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which among the following are non-primitive datatypes?",
    answer: "Array and Scanner",
    options: [
      "Array",
      "int",
      "char",
      "Scanner"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the options can be used to get the size of an array?",
    answer: "arr.length",
    options: [
      "arr.size ",
      "arr.length ",
      "lengthof(arr)",
      "None of these",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the return type of charAt() function in String class?",
    answer: "char",
    options: [
      "int",
      "char",
      "void",
      "float ",
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "How can we declare a 2d array with 4 rows but the number of columns in each row are not set?",
      answer: "int a[][]=new int [4][];",
      options: [
        "int a[][]=new int [4][];",
        "int a[]=new int[4][];",
        "int a[][]=new int[4];",
        "int a[][]=new int [][4];"
      
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "How can we access the last element in last row in a 5*5 2-D array arr?",
      answer: "arr[4][4]",
      options: [
        "arr[5][5]",
        "arr[4][4]",
        "arr[5][4]",
        "arr[4][5]"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which access modifier can be used to access a variable outside the class and within the package?",
    answer: "public and default",
    options: [
      "public",
      "private",
      "protected",
      "default",
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
    question: "Which of these operators is used to allocate memory for an object?",
    answer: "new",
    options: [
      "malloc",
      "alloc",
      "new",
      "give",
    ]
},
{
  numb: 8,
  question: "Which of the modifier can't be used for constructors ?",
  answer: "static",
  options: [
    "public",
    "static",
    "private",
    "protected"
]
},
{
  numb: 9,
  question: "Which keyword works as a reference to the current Object whose Method or constructor is being invoked ?",
  answer: "this",
  options: [
    "import",
    "catch",
    "abstract",
    "this"
]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "Which keyword is used to inherit a class?",
  answer: "extends",
  options: [ 
    "inherits",
    "extends",
    "imports",
    "none of these"
]
},

];